panarmenian.net 2012-12-09

# Armenian News - PanARMENIAN.Net

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

**_Privacy policy_**

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We will make readily available to visitors information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

**_Cookies_  
**

Like most interactive web sites PanARMENIAN.Net uses cookies to enable us to retrieve user details for each visit. Cookies are used in some areas of our site to enable the functionality of this area and ease of use for those people visiting. Some of our affiliate partners may also use cookies.

**_Our Commitment To Data Security_**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

| 

 **  Contact us**

**Editorial**  
News tips and information:  
editorial@panarmenian.net  
Comments and suggestions:  
comments@panarmenian.net  
(+374) 10 553623, 91 553623  
(+374) 10 556118, 91 556118

**Management**  
info@panarmenian.net  
(+374) 10 551749  
(+374) 91 551749

**PanARMENIAN Photo agency**  
photo@panarmenian.net  
(+374) 10 571890

**Public Relations and Marketing**  
pr@panarmenian.net  
(+374) 10 551749

**Advertisement and Sales**  
ad@panarmenian.net  
(+374) 10 551749

**Human Resources**  
vacancy@panarmenian.net

**Common issues**  
support@panarmenian.net

 Address

"PanARMENIAN Media" LLC

5, Aleq Manukian str. (House of Radio)  
0025, Yerevan, Armenia  
  
---|---
